{
    "id": "f61bd212250b48ee994974f25e184dcd",
    "title": "Contracted forms exercise",
    "exercises": [
        {
            "id": "8a8ae9883fb74925be14893843cdf120",
            "title": "Contractions Exercise",
            "questions": [
                {
                    "question": "She’s never been to the US.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "She's = she has",
                        "She's = she is"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "There’s someone at the door.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "There's = there is",
                        "There's =there has"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "The dog is happy. It’s had its breakfast.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "It's = it is",
                        "It's = it has"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "He’s not interested in the offer.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "He's = he is",
                        "He's = he has"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "There’s a problem.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "There's = there is",
                        "There's = there has"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "She’s from Mexico.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "She's = she is",
                        "She's = she has"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "He’s gone to the market.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "He's = he has",
                        "He's = he is"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "It’s a sad state of affairs.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "It's = it is",
                        "It's = it has"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "There’s been an explosion near the temple.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "There's = there is",
                        "There's = there has"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "She’s returned from her business tour.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "She's = she has",
                        "She's = she is"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                }
            ]
        }
    ]
}